

PROFILE

I am currently studying a Diploma in Web & UX Design at YooBee School of Design, due to graduate in December 2018. I have had 10 years of administration experience prior to taking this year to switch up my career path and study something I am passionate about.

CONTACT



021 240 6888



claireu@ymail.com



LinkedIn - Claire Stark



clairestark.co.nz

SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS/SCSS
- JavaScript + Libraries
- Google Maps/Leaflet
- Data Visualisation
- CRM WordPress
- Attention to detail

SYSTEMS/PROGRAMS

Sublime Text 3, GitHub, Command Line, Node.js, Google Drive, Dropbox, Mac OS, Windows 10 OS, Xero, SAP

CMS:

Sitefinity, Django, Sugar, WordPress

REFERENCES

Available on request

CLAIRE STARK

Web Design & Development

EDUCATION

YOOBEE SCHOOL OF DESIGN

2018

Diploma in Web & UX Design

CODECADEMY

2016 & 2017

Self learning course HTML5 & CSS Self learning course Javascript

EXPERIENCE

MYAGENT - ACCOUNTS MANAGER

February 2018 - Present

• Responsible for AP, AR and Reconciliations (part-time during studies)

MYAGENT - OFFICE MANAGER

May 2015 - February 2018

- Sole responsibility for daily operations of the office.
- Management of bookings/calendars for the 20+ contractors.
- Full AP,AR and Payroll, for Myagent, but also, it's other smaller companies such as The Property Crowd and Four-Wall's.
- Responsible for upkeep Myagents website, as well as content loading to microsites for clients.
- The go-to person for other employees and extremely knowledgeable in all our systems.

TECHDAY - OFFICE MANAGER

February 2015 - May 2015

- Sole responsibility for the daily operations of the office.
- Management of bookings, content loading to various websites.
- AP & AR for the business

Systems Used:

Google Double Click for Publishers, Trello, Django CMS, FileMaker, HootSuite, Xero

VARIOUS - ADMINISTRATION

2009 - 2015

- Responsible for running of daily operations of offices.
- Extremely proficient in simplifying day to day processes.
- The go to person at all of the companies I've worked for.
- AP & AR for businesses.
- Various administration duties.

Companies:

House of Travel Holdings, UGL Limited, Service Engineers, The Radiology Group